（アギエル）ベヘモット３４柱師団柱将
アギエルちゃんだよ。
I'm Agiel-chan! A Pillar General
of Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division!
（神崎・姫川）はあ？
（オドネル）同じく柱将　オドネル。
And I am also a Pillar General, Odonel.
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division - Pillar General (Once Again)
Odonel
（ゼラ）柱将　ゼラ。
Pillar General, Zela.
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division - Pillar General
Zela
（アギエル）むさ苦しいな～。
あ？
Well, look what the cat dragged in!
（ドスン！）
言い忘れてたけど　進入禁止だよ。
Maybe I forgot to mention this...
...but trespassing is forbidden.
（石動）むんっ。でや～っ！
Kannagi.
Shigetsu Sword School Style Eighth Style
Kannagi
（早乙女）そいつは　つまり→
In other words, you're here for a
declaration of war, aren't you, Behemoth?
宣戦布告ってことだよな…
ベヘモット。
（寧々）なっ！
（アギエル）１人２人くらい→
殺してもいいよね！
あ…。
But I'm sure it won't matter
if I kill one or two!
（邦枝）間一髪…間に合ったわね。
In the nick of time...
I made it.
葵ねえさん！
何だ　お前？
Madame Aoi!
Who are you?
もう一度　確認するけど…→
Let me double check something...
本当に普通の人には
見えないんでしょうね。
You definitely can't be seen
by normal people, right?
（コマちゃん）
当然や。葵ちゃんかて
最初は見えへんかったやろ。
Exactly!
You couldn't see me at
first either, remember?
わかったわ。
Got it.
最初から全力で行くわよ。
We're going all out from the start!
We're the Strongest!
（古市）なんだ？邦枝先輩の周りに
何かいるような…。
What? I can sense there's something
around Kunieda-senpai...
（アギエル）ん～ふむふむ。→
珍しいものを飼ってるね
お嬢ちゃん。→
Looks like you've got
quite the rare pet, Missy.
魔力っぽいものを感じるけど
そいつは悪魔かな？
Feels almost like Demon Power there...
Is that guy a Demon?
（オドネル）
シーカリオン…大昔に
人間界に移り住んだ悪魔種族だ。→
The Shikalion... A race of Demons that
went to live in the Human World long ago.
今では祓魔の獣神の使いなどと
呼ばれているらしいが。
Now they are said to be beast gods
used for exorcisms, or something.
（アギエル）おっ　詳しいね　オドネル。
You know your stuff, Odonel!
（オドネル）フン。しょせんは
魔界の生存競争に敗れて→
In the end they were defeated in the harsh
battle for survival that is the Demon World,
人間の飼い犬に成り下がった
弱小種族だ。なんなら私が…。
and let themselves become the dogs
of humans. A race of weaklings.
Therefore, allow me.
アタシの獲物だよ。手出しすんな。
This is my prey.
Don't even think about it.
（邦枝）なんて殺気…
これがベヘモット３４柱師団。
What an incredible murderous aura... So this
is Behemoth's 34 Pillars Division...
（コマちゃん）葵ちゃん。→
Aoi-chan...
やっぱ　あの眼鏡っ娘ええなぁ～。
スリーサイズどれぐらいやろ？
That glasses girl there sure is a cutie...
I wonder what her measurements are?
うん。だからもう
その話はいいから。
Sure. But enough about that.
悪魔野学園とか言ったわね。
You said you are from Akumano Academy?
にょ？
（邦枝）あなたたち　いったい
何を　たくらんでいるの？
What in the world are you people plotting?
ここは私たちの学校よ。
This is our school!
出て行くのは
あなたたちの方だわっ！
You're the ones who should leave!
言っとくけど
アタシらは　ただの見張りよ。
Just so you know, we're only the lookouts.
他の団員たちが来るまで
ここの管理を任されているだけさ。
We're just holding down the fort until
the rest of the division shows up.
他の団員？
そう…。
The rest of the division?
Right!
（ベヘモット）即ちベヘモット３４柱師団
総勢３９４人…。
In other words, Behemoth's 34 Pillars
Division, all 394 members...
（ベル坊）ん～ニョダ…。
（男鹿）
ベル坊　ちょっと静かにしてろ。
Baby Beel... Be quiet, would you?
（ヒルダ）坊っちゃま　おなかを
空かせておられるのですね。
Master... You must be hungry.
ニョダダ　ブィーッ！
（早乙女・一刀斎・石動）あっ！
（ドスン！）
にょ？
（ベヘモット）つまり…。→
Therefore...
貴様の学校は文字通り
悪魔たちの学園になるのじゃ。→
Your school will become an academy
for Demons, just like the name says!
男鹿辰巳。
てめえが…→
Oga Tatsumi...
So... you're Behemoth?
ベヘモットかよ…。
悪魔たちの学園…。
An academy for Demons? What's the
point of doing something like that?
そんなもの作って
何をするつもり？
ふうん。
アンタ　いい目をしてるね。
I like the look in your eyes.
学校　学校って…なんで
そんなに　こだわるか→
I don't get why you're so hung up
about this school thing, though.
わかんないけど…
団長の言った通りだわ。
But it's just as our leader said...
ここにいれば　おもしろいヤツと
いっぱいやれそう…だっ！
Come here, and there'll
be plenty of fun people!
（コマちゃん）くるでっ。
Here she comes.
アハッ　いい反応！
Good reaction!
まだまだ。いくよっ！
But I'm not done yet!
ふん！
あぁっ！
（オドネル）アギエル！
ととっ…。
Agiel!
普通の獣か…危ない危ない。
An exorcism beast, huh?
Gotta watch out for that.
な～んか…燃えてきちゃった。
I'm kinda gettin' fired up!
（姫川）おい　邦枝！
オレたちも加勢するぜ！
Hey, Kunieda!
We're gonna join in.
（神崎）おうっ！
（古市）ちょ…２人ともいいから！
Yeah!
Wait! You guys don't have to...
（アギエル）そっちはいいわ。アタシ
弱いヤツに興味ないし。
He's right!
I don't care 'bout weaklings.
（邦枝）聞き捨てならないわね。
I'm not gonna let that slide.
うちのクラスに弱いヤツなんて…
１人もいないわっ！
There's not a single person
in our class... that's weak!
コマちゃん。
おう　やるか。
Koma-chan.
Sure, we doing it?
（アギエル）お～！なんだ　なんだ？
What's this?
必殺技か？いいね　いいね。→
Some kinda secret move?
Cool, cool!
じゃあ　アタシも。
Then, I'll join in the fun!
（アギエル）学校作って　何するかって…
決まってんじゃん。
What are we doing creating a school, you ask?
Isn't it obvious?
戦争だよっ！
It's war!
（アギエル）暗黒剣！ブラッディグレイブ！！
Darkness Sword...
Bloody Grave!
（邦枝）心月流抜刀術弐式…→
Shingetsu sword school, second style.
百花乱れ桜。魔装…。
Countless Petals, Scattering Sakura Blossoms.
Demon Clad... Dazzling Flower Blizzard!
これは…かまいたち。
（ドサッ）
This is... kamaitachi?
（邦枝）戦争がどうとか言ったわね。
You said something about a war, didn't you?
受けて立つわ。
石矢魔なめんじゃないわよ！
We're on! Don't underestimate Ishiyama!
ポロリは？
ないわよっ。
No wardrobe malfunction?
Not a chance.
（ゾンビの声）
あっ。
今度は　なに？
なっ　なんだ　こいつら…。
What is it now?
Who the hell are these guys?
てめえがベヘモット…つまり→
So you're Behemoth...
In other words, I'm up against
the big boss right off the bat!
いきなり大将の
お出ましってわけか。
…違います。
あ？だって　お前
ベヘモットだろ？
No.
But you just said you're Behemoth!
全然　違います。
いやいや　だって　お前
ベヘモットだろ？
You are completely wrong.
But you just said! You're Behemoth!
人違いです。
てめえ…。
プーッ！
You have the wrong person.
Why, you...
（ベヘモット）本当のことじゃよ。
It's the truth.
たしかにベヘモット３４柱師団は
わしが作った組織じゃ。→
It's true that I am the one who created
Behemoth's 34 Pillars Division.
が　わしも歳じゃ。引退して大将は
ソイツにまかせておる。
But at my age I've retired,
and I've place him in command.
あ…。
ダ…。
（夏目）
いや～大変なことになったね～。→
Well, this has gotten quite troublesome.
まさか　石矢魔の校舎が
乗っ取られるなんて。→
Never would have thought Ishiyama's
school building would be occupied.
全面戦争って
こういうことだったんだね～。
All out war...
I guess this is what it's like!
（神崎）どりゃっ！
（姫川）ちやっ！
（城山）ふんっ！
（寧々）でや～！
（古市）ひえ～っ！
（神崎）つ～か　きりねぇぞ　これ。
（姫川）ゾンビ映画かよ！
Yeah but... There's no end to 'em!
Is this some zombie movie?
コマちゃん　まとめて行くわよ。
Koma-chan, we'll clean them out all at once.
（古市）待って下さい！邦枝先輩。→
Wait, Kunieda-senpai!
こいつら…
石矢魔の生徒ですよ！→
They're...
...Ishiyama's students!
聖石矢魔以外の学校に
転校したはずの…。
The ones that transferred to
schools other than St. Ishiyama!
（焔王）ぴったしカンカンじゃ！→
Survey says: Bingo!
たしかに　そやつらは
貴様らの仲間だった者たち。→
It's true! These guys were
once your "comrades".
だが今は　余の忠実な
しもべたちじゃ。
But now they are completely my servants!
この声は…。
That voice...!
（古市）焔王！
（焔王）
フフフ…久しぶりじゃの～古市。
Lord En!
It's been a while, Furuichi!
（ジャバウォック）
おやじ　そろそろ時間だ。→
Pops, it's about time.
焔王のクソガキが
かんしゃく起こすぜ。
That brat Lord En's gonna lose his temper.
（ベヘモット）こらこら　主君をクソガキ
呼ばわりするな　ジャバウォック。
Hey! Don't call our master
a brat, Jabberwock.
こいつが　狂竜ジャバウォック。
He's Jabberwock the Mad Dragon!
ん？女　なんのつもりだ　そりゃ？
あ？
Woman, what are you doing?
（ジャバウォック）ソドム…。
Sodom.
いかん！
Oh, no!
（ソドム）ギシャアーッ！
ヒルダーっ！
Hilda!!
The brat said not to chomp her,
and to bring her back alive.
噛み殺すなよ
生かして連れて帰るよう→
クソガキに言われてんだ。
Hold it, you!
待て　コラッ！！この～っ！
ジャバウォック…
噂以上にイカれた野郎だな。→
Jabberwock...
You're more nuts than the rumors said.
What're you planning to do by capturing her?
その女を捕らえて　どうする？
早乙女禅十郎…対戦の覇者か。
Saotome Zenjuro.
Champion of the great war?
女は殺しはせん。
しばらく預かるだけだ。
I won't kill the woman.
I'm just taking her for a bit.
Let me go!
はなせっ！
ダーアダブッ！
Stop it. You cannot win fighting here.
やめろ　ここで戦っても勝てぬ。
（ジャバウォック）それよりアンタと
一度　手合わせしたいね。
Although, I do wish to go
a round with you sometime.
No need to worry. My pupil
will come calling before long!
安心しろ。うちの弟子が近々
お礼参りに行くからよ。
そこで　わめいてるガキがか？→
You mean the little brat whining over there?
ハハハッ！
期待しないで待ってるよ。
I'll wait, but I ain't expectin' much!
Let me go.
はなせよ…。
はなせっつってんだろ～っ！
アイーッ！
I said let me go!
Hey, you little shit!
（神崎）てめえ　こらガキ！
ど～ゆうこった　これは！
What the hell's the meaning of this?
Yeah, yeah!
（由加）そ～だ　そ～だ！
ふっふふ…。
This is our school!
（寧々）
ここはアタシたちの学校だよ！
とっとと出て行きなっ！
Now get out!
（由加）そ～だ　そ～だ！
Yeah, yeah!
（姫川）
だいたい　何でうちの学校のもんが
てめ～のしもべなんだよ！→
And why the hell are our
students your servants?
How much?! How much did you pay 'em off?!
いくらだ！？いくらで買収した！？
（由加）そ～だ　そ～だ！
Yeah, yeah!
Coatl...
コアトルー。
（ケツァルコアトル）よしよし。
There, there.
Um, pardon the tardiness.
え～　申し遅れました。私は
ベヘモット３４柱師団　柱爵→
I am Quetzalcoatl, a Pillar Master
of Behemoth's 34 Pillars Division.
ケツァルコアトルと申します。
まず最初に→
First thing, your former
comrades were not bought off.
あなた方のお仲間たち。これは
買収したわけでは　ありません。→
私が　ある方法で操っております。
故に　彼らは→
Rather, I am controlling them
with a special technique.
Currently, they only follow
our orders.
私か坊っちゃまの言うことしか
聞きません。そして坊っちゃまは→
And Master says this:
こう　おっしゃっています。
「お前たちの学校も仲間も→
I have taken your
school and your friends.
余が預かった。返してほしくば
余と勝負しろ」と。
If you want them back, you will fight me.
勝負？
Fight?
（ケツァルコアトル）
この学園の　いたる所に
ステージが用意してあります。→
Stages have been prepared inside the school.
そして我々　柱師団の誰かが
待ち受けている。→
And there, members of our Pillars
Division will be waiting for you.
つまり　これは…ゲームです！
坊っちゃまの大好きな→
In other words...
...this is a game! My Master's favorite.
あの時　つかなかった
ゲームの決着を→
The game that went unfinished
the last time...
愛と　誇りと　絆と　友と
そして…命をかけて。
Put your love, pride, bonds, friends, and...
...your lives on the line!
（ベヘモット）どうじゃった？男鹿辰巳…あの契約者は。
What did you think about that
contract holder, Oga Tatsumi?
（ジャバウォック）あぁ　話にならねえな
飛びかかってこれりゃあ→
Not even worth my time.
I suspected he'd come leaping at me, but...
少しは見込みもあったが…
ま　唯一の期待は→
I suppose that hope was 'cause
he's that Zenjuro's pupil.
禅十郎の弟子ってとこだけか。
≪勝手なこと
言ってんじゃねえよ≫
How about you shut the hell up?
You think I'll let you get away?!
逃がすかよ　ボケが。
ダブッ！
ほう…意外だな　まさか
追ってこれるとは思わなかった。→
That's surprising! Never thought
you'd actually chase after me.
（ジャバウォック）そんなに女が大事か？
男鹿辰巳。
Is this woman really that
important to you, Oga Tatsumi?
Is that what I should say?
だっけか？
行くぜ　ベル坊。→
Here we go, Baby Beel! We'll show
him the fruits of our training!
特訓の成果　見せてやるぜ！アイ　ダブッ！
スーパーミルクタイム
３０ｃｃ！
Super Milk Time...
30cc!
ほぅ…。
親父　手ぇ出すなよ。
Pops, stay outta this.
勝手にしろ。
Suit yourself.
くらえ　ゼブルエンブレム
３連鎖！
Take this! Zebel Emblem!
Triple Hit!
なんだ？何が起こっている！？
What? What happened?
（ジャバウォック）ふ～ん…禅十郎の弟子
ってのは本当らしいな。
Looks like you really are Zenjuro's pupil.
《ウッ…こいつ　爆発を正面から
受けて　跳ね返しやがった》
This bastard took the explosions
face on and repelled them?
ウッ…ベル坊！
ビェ！
Baby Beel!
50cc!
５０ｃｃ！
なるほど。そいつを飲むと
魔力が上がるのか。
I see...
The more you drink, the more
your Demon Power rises...
ワーッ！
Drink more!
もっと飲め。オレを楽しませろ。
Let me have some fun here!
《目が　かすんできやがった。→
My vision... it's getting cloudy...
これ以上飲めば
確実に意識が飛ぶ…》
If I drink any more, I really
will lose consciousness...
Fool!
バカモノッ！飲むな！
この前のように→
Don't drink it!
You have no way of knowing
you'll win this time!
勝てる確証はないのだぞ！
私のことは　いい。→
Don't worry about me! Don't
think about beating this man!
その男を倒そうなどと考えるな！
Take Master and get away from here!
貴様は　坊っちゃまを連れて帰れ！
ヘッ…確かにな。てめえとの
勝負は　また次だ。
She has a point.
I'll fight you another time.
Sorry, but I'm gonna have
to high-tail it today.
悪いが　今日は
ズラからせてもらうぜ。
Let Hilda go, you shitty dragon!
ヒルダを離しやがれ
クソドラゴン！！
Zebel Emblem...
ゼブルエンブレム
６連鎖！
Sextuple Hit!
ウッ！
ギィーーー！！
うっ…。
All right!
よしっ！
アダッ！
バカが…ソドムを
怒らせやがったな。
Idiot...
He's pissed off Sodom.
ギィシャァァー！！
簡単に捕まってんじゃねえよ。
ダブ。
Don't let yourself get captured like that.
バカモノ。
Fools.
おぉっ！
一度しか言わんから
よく聞け。
I'm only saying this once, so listen well.
あ？
Take care of the Master.
坊っちゃまを　頼んだぞ。
貴様は　この人間界で
たった１人の父親だ。
You...
...are the only parent he
has in this Human World.
ミルクの残りは　これだけ…かよ。
This is all... the milk I have left?
ダブッ！
ダブッ！ナ…。
ダーブ！
コロッケ？
Croquettes?
((フン　感謝して敬え。
ついでだから→
Be grateful.
I even put in some dessert for you.
デザートも　つけてやった))
デザートって…コロッケかよ！
Dessert? She meant croquettes?
ダッ！ギャーオ！
Baby Beel!
ベル坊…お前　何やってんの！？
What are you doing?
そうか！スーパーミルクタイムは
オレが　魔界の食べ物→
I see! Super Milk Time is when
I drink Demon World milk.
ベル坊のミルクを飲むことで
悪魔と人間の境界を曖昧にし→
A technique to blur the boundaries of Human
and Demon and increase our synchronization rate!
シンクロ率を高める技…だったら
逆に　ベル坊が人間界の食べ物→
So if Baby Beel eats Human World food,
オレの好物のコロッケを食べても同じことが起こるってことか！
like my favorite croquettes,
the same thing should happen, right?
つまり…スーパーコロッケタイム！！
In other words...
It's Super Croquette Time!
Super Croquette Time
お…あっ！
坊っちゃま…。
Master...
Hurry up already.
（男鹿ベル）早くしろ。
クェェェーー！！
めんどくせえ…もういい
食っちまえ　ソドム！→
What a pain.
Enough! Eat them, Sodom!
I hate things like "effort",
"friendship", "triumph"!
オレは　努力・友情・勝利ってやつ
が大嫌いなんだよ～！！
おっ…。
I'm gonna tell you something.
ひとつ教えといてやる。努力なんかじゃねえ…。
This ain't effort.
オレ達は　はじめから…。
We were...
（男鹿ベル）最強なんだ！
...the strongest from the start!
うぉぉぉ～～！！
Right hand on violet!
（焔王）右手が赤ムラサキ。
お～！
Left leg on purplish red!
（焔王）左足がドドメ色！
Nice... Nice, Aoi-chan.
（コマちゃん）ええで　ええで葵ちゃん。
So, wait...
てゆ～か…これが
命を　かけたゲーム！？
This is the game we're risking our lives with?
（ソドム）ギェェェーー！！
（破壊音）
うぉ～…。
Jabberwock!
ジャバウォック！なにを
しておるのじゃ！
What the hell have you done?!
せっかく　いい感じで
ゲームが進んでおったのに！
I finally had a good game going!
お！？
あっ！
あ！？
男鹿…。
Oga?
All of you, get back.
お前らは下がってろ。
よせ　愚か者！そのまま力を
解放したら　貴様と坊っちゃまは…。
Stop this, fool!
If you continue to use such power,
you and the Master will...
心配ねえ…男鹿辰巳は
人間界で　たった１人の→
Don't worry. Oga Tatsumi is the only parent
Baby Beel's got in the Human World, right?
ベル坊の親なんだろ？だったら信じろ！
Then, believe!
I'll take 'em all... and blow 'em away!
全部まとめて…ぶっ飛ば～す！
おぉぉ～！！
（一同）お～…。
男鹿…。
Oga?
Oga!
（邦枝）男鹿～！！
Where did Oga and Baby Beel go?
He's such an idiot, making
us worry like this!
Kunieda-senpai, are you crying?
N-No, I'm not!
I was just cutting some onions, is all!
Why are you cutting onions
at a time like this?
On the next Beelzebub:
I Won't Say Goodbye.
It's finally the last episode, Baby Beel!
Oga Tatsumi, Beel-chan...
We won't forget you!
And, our battle starts now!